您好，漂亮的人们欢迎您参加这一节关于Linux文件系统的课程。
Hello you beautiful people are welcome to this section of the course on the Linux file system.
好的。
OK.
在这一节中，您将学习一大堆命令，这些命令将向您展示如何
So with this section you're going to be learning a whole load of commands that will show you how to
使用Linux命令行操作文件。
manipulate files using the Linux command line.
然后，我们将从讨论Linux文件系统和实际文件是什么开始
And then we're going to start off by talking about the Linux file system and what files actually are
从文件系统的角度来看。
from the file systems perspective.
当您理解了这一点后，您将继续讨论如何在文件中移动
And when you understand that you're going to move on to discussing how you can move around the file
系统并使用命令行创建文件。
system and create files using the command line.
然后，您将学习一整套新命令，如复制、重命名、删除、移动、粘贴、搜索
Then you'll learn a whole host of new commands such as copying renaming deleting moving pasting searching
对于整个文件系统中的文件查看文件搜索文件中的文本排序数据和
for files across a whole file system viewing files searching for text within files sorting data and
此外，还将创建用于存储的文件备份和归档，以及您将在本教程中学习的命令
also creating file backups and archives for storage and the commands that you're going to learn in this
部分功能非常强大，并提供了许多选项和方式供您自定义其行为。
section are super powerful and come with a lot of options and ways for you to customize their behavior.
这很棒，但也是一个非常有用的提示不用担心记住所有不同的命令选项
Which is great but is a super useful tip Don't worry about memorizing all the different command options
，而不是只了解每个命令存在的可能性，并知道
in this section but instead just learn about the possibilities that exist for each command and know
这些视频、提供的小抄和命令手册页面将始终可用
that these videos the cheat sheets that are provided and the commands manual pages will always be available
供您参考。
for you to use as reference.
所以我希望你们能和我一样兴奋，因为在这个部分结束后，你们将会有很多
So I hope hope you are as excited as I am because after the section you're going to have a whole lot
要在您的管道中使用的新命令。
of new commands to use in your pipelines.
还可以与整台计算机交互，在全新的计算机中完成99%的日常工作
Also be able to interact with your whole computer and do 99 percent of your daily work in a whole new
这样，您就会发现，使用在本节中学到的技术，您会更快地找到它们
way and you'll find that with the techniques that you learn in this section you'll find them much faster
比您现在最可能使用的图形方法更强大、更有效。
more powerful and more effective than the graphical methods that you'll most likely using right now.
如果你像我一样，你很可能再也不会回去了。
And if you're like me you'll likely never go back.
好的，能成为这门课程中真正革命性的一部分是件好事，感觉无情就是能力。
OK so it's good to be a really revolutionary section of the Course feel inexorability is abilities.
我会在下一个视频里见到你的。
All that goodness I'll see you in the next video.